A Guide to the Constituent Correspondence of XX, 1992.
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Constituent Correspondence of XX,
1992.
The Library of Virginia
34587
Virginia. Governor (1990-1994: XX).
XX cu. ft. (XX boxes)
Administrative Information
Arranged by series.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession 34587 was transferred by XXX, XX.
Historical Information
XX
XX
Scope and Content
XX
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Cabinet Secretaries and State Agencies, 1992
Series II. Governor's Office, 1992
Series III. Scheduling Office, 1992.
Contents List
- Series I. Cabinet Secretaries and State Agencies, 1992.
  - Secretary of Administration: Compensation Board, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Administration: Health insurance benefits, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Administration: Health insurance benefits, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Administration: Health insurance benefits, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Administration: Health insurance benefits, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Administration: Dept. of Planning and Budget - Salaries, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Administration: Dept. of Planning and Budget - Salaries, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Administration: Early retirement, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Administration: Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Administration: Equal Employment Services, Office of, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Administration: Equal Employment Services, Office of, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Administration: Equal Employment Services, Office of, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Administration: General, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Administration: General, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Administration: General, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Administration: General Services, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Administration: General Services, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Administration: Grievances, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Administration: Human Rights, Council on, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Administration: Information Management, Council on, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Administration: Information Technology, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Administration: Information Technology, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Administration: Key Advantage Plan, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Administration: Key Advantage Plan, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Secretary of Administration: Key Advantage Plan, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Secretary of Administration: Key Advantage Plan, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Secretary of Administration: Key Advantage Plan, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Secretary of Administration: Key Advantage Plan, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Secretary of Administration: Key Advantage Plan, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Secretary of Administration: Key Advantage Plan, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Administration: Key Advantage Plan, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Administration: Key Advantage Plan, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Administration: Key Advantage Plan, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Administration: Key Advantage Plan, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Administration: Local Government, Commission on, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Administration: Purchase and Supply, Division of, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Administration: Retirement System, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Administration: State Board of Elections, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Administration: Veterans Affairs, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Administration: Veterans Affairs, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Administration: Veterans Affairs, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Administration: Virginia Supplemental Retirement, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Agriculture, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Agriculture, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Auctions, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Block grants, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Board for Contractors, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Commerce, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Commerce, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Consumer Affairs, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Consumer Affairs, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Defense, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Forestry, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Division of Tourism, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Fruit Crop Disaster Area, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing and Community Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing and Community Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing and Community Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing and Community Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing and Community Development, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing and Community Development, Dept. of - Homeless, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing and Urban Development, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing Partnership Program, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: JETRO, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Labor and Industry, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Low Income Housing Tax Credit Program, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Minority Business, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: NASA Space Station, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Pickett Road Tank Farm, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Pickett Road Tank Farm, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Real estate, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Redskin Stadium, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Redskin Stadium, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Redskin Stadium, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Redskin Stadium, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Redskin Stadium, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Redskin Stadium, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Relocate to Virginia, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Rural Development, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Rural Development, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Small Business, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Southeast Japan Conference, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Economic Development Corporation (VEDCORP), 1992. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Agricultural Development, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Board for Cosmetology, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Employment Commission, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Employment Commission, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Employment Commission, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Employment Commission, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Employment Commission, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Employment Commission, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Employment Commission, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Festival of American Film, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Housing Partnership Program, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Housing Partnership Program, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Pesticide Control Board, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Port Authority, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Rice Commission, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: World Trade, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: World Trade, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: World Trade, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Secretary of Education: Center for Innovative Technology (CIT), 1992. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Education: Child abuse in schools, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Education: Christopher Newport College, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Education: Clinch Valley Community College, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Education: College of William and Mary, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Education: Commission on Educational Opportunities for All Virginians, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Education: Commnunity Colleges, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Education: Council on Higher Education for Virginia, State, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Education: Dropout prevention, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Secretary of Education: Extension Services (Form letters), 1992. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Education: George Mason University, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Education: Governor's School Program, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Education: Governor's School Program, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Education: Gunston Hall, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Education: James Madison University, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Education: Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Education: Library Aid (Form letters), 1992. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Education: Longwood College, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Education: Mary Washington College, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Education: National Air and Space Museum, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Education: National Science Foundation, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Education: Norfolk State University, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Education: Northern Virginia Community College, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Education: Old Dominion University, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Education: Radford University, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Education: School boards, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Education: School funding, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Education: School violence prevention, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Education: Science Museum of Virginia, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Education: State budget cuts, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Education: State Education Assistance Authority, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Education: Teacher salaries, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Education: Tuition Assistance Grants, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Secretary of Education: Tuition Assistance Grants, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Secretary of Education: University of Virginia, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Commonwealth College System, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Commonwealth University, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Cooperative Extention Service, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Education Loan Authority, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Military Institute, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Secretary of Education: Virgina State Library and Archives, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia State University, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Union University, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Secretary of Finance: Accounts, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Finance: Cigarette tax, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Finance: Economic Advisory Council, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Finance: Escheator, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Finance: Food tax, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Finance: Income tax assessment, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Finance: Income tax assessment, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Finance: Income tax assessment, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Finance: Income tax assessment, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Finance: Income tax assessment, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Finance: Internal Auditor, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Finance: Mail order tax, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Finance: Office of the Comptroller, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Finance: Pensions, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Finance: Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Finance: Property tax, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Finance: Real estate tax, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Finance: Retirement tax, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Finance: Sales tax, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Finance: Social Security tax, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Finance: State budget revenues, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Finance: State Lottery proceeds, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Secretary of Finance: Treasury, Dept. of the, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Abortion, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Adolescent pregnancy, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Adoption, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Aging, Dept. for the, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Aging, Dept. for the, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Aid to Dependent Children (ADC), 1992. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: AIDS/HIV, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Board of Medicine, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Board of Optometry, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Bureau of Vital Records, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Central State Hospital, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Central Virginia Training Center, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Certificate of Public Need, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child Abuse, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child custody, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child custody, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child support, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child support, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child support, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Commission on Health Care for All Virginians, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Community Service Block Grants, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Council on Child Day Care, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Council on Human Rights, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Council on Indians, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Council on the Status of Women, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Council on Youth and Family Services, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Deaf and Hard of Hearing, Dept. for the, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Eastern State Hospital, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Emergency Medical Services, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Family Support Act, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Food Bank, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Governor's Employment and Training Dept., 1992. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health Care, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health Care, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health Care, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health Care, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health Care, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health Professions, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health Professions, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health Service Cost Review Council, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Indoor Clean Air Act, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Infant mortality, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Job Training Partnership Act, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Medical Assistance Services, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Medicare, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 22)